(July 2026, somewhere in Southeast Asia)
The weather is so great.
(Hyun Moo enjoying some rest after a long time)
I should've done this more often.
I'm generous.
Where's Joon?
(Loud horns honking on the road)
My gosh!
Hey, hey.
I think we're going to bump into them.
Gosh, we almost died.
Wait. It's scary here.
Just don't go. It's super scary.
Wait!
(Joon is screaming)
(I give you my peace.)
(Am I dreaming?)
(Korea’s first-ever interview conducted lying down)
I dozed off two times.
This is crazy.
(This is getting aired, right?)
(To our surprise, it is being aired.)
(We have a clear standard...)
(for travel.)
(This is Hyunmoo Road's making of a new travel route)
(There is no set path.)
(The path we take is the path of romance.)
(This is the vibe I love.)
(If you hate it, don't do it.)
(It's the new way of travel nobody expected.)
(They will go to all corners of the world.)
(And they will discover their own route.)
(There is nobody.)
(We throw ourselves into the crowd. That is what travel is all about.)
(Current time AM 07:00 The morning energy is fabulous!)
(A locally immersive variety show is born.)
(The essence of local travel)
(Overflowing with romance)
(This is Hyunmoo Road sets sail!)
(3 days ago)
(Incheon International Airport)
Hello.
I am Jun Hyun Moo, the rookie YouTuber.
(Jun Hyun Moo gives a shot at being a YouTuber!)
I love travelling, you see.
Seeing the way I travel, my friends...
said I should film my travels as a YouTube content.
They said I should document and share...
my stress-free trip with people.
(How does he travel?)
Goodness, I loved this.
Barcelona.
This was where my journey began.
I drove 900km.
(He drove 900km.)
The week after was the week of the Cannes Film Festival.
I was curious about what it would be like there.
I love driving, so I decided to drive there.
On the way, I passed by Carcassonne.
I stopped by Marseille...
and also Saint-Tropez.
It's the vacation spot featured in "Emily in Paris."
I saw the signage and stopped by the place.
(He accidentally ran into a place featured in a drama.)
(Do you have no standard at all?)
I always have a standard.
For shopping, I go to Tokyo.
For eating good food, I go to Fukuoka.
If I want to go for a nice drive, I go to Sapporo.
That's my standard.
I may not have a plan, but I do have a standard.
(Jun Hyun Moo's world travel map)
You see, people see me as...
someone who pushes the limit.
People who like me must be those who push the limit.
I will call them "Moo Friends."
Dear Moo Friends, why don't you join me on my reckless trip?
Wouldn't that be fun?
I will kick things off with big ambitions.
I will be boarding soon.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea to go there in this weather.
Today, I'm headed to...
none other than...
Da Nang.
(Hyunmoo Road's first destination: Da Nang, Vietnam)
(It's a vacation spot located in Central Vietnam.)
(It is also one of the most beloved vacation, healing spot of Koreans.)
(This is why they call it "Da Nang of Gyeonggi Province.")
(The large Korean tourist population made it like a Korean city.)
(Aren’t Da Nang itineraries all pretty predictable?)
(Find a spot with no Koreans in Da Nang, Gyeonggi Province.)
(They will explore a new spot you have never seen before.)
(They will go to the vacation spots only the locals go.)
(There are Korean tourists here?)
(There is no set route. The path they forge is Hyunmoo Road.)
(What happens if they run into Koreans?)
(Have a great trip!)
(Thank you.)
(If they encounter Koreans, it means they failed.)
(It doesn't meet our standard.)
(If they run into a Korean, the shoot is over.)
We’ll only show you trips that meet our standards.
(Da Nang International Airport)
(What kind of trip will be awaiting us?)
(Da Nang Local Time: 10:30pm)
It's hot.
(You can feel the heat with your entire body.)
(Let's see.)
Current temperature in Da Nang.
(The current temperature in Da Nang is...)
It's 30 degrees Celsius, and it's night.
(Da Nang Current Weather Temperature 30°C)
The humidity is 70 percent.
But it feels like 41°C.
And it's the middle of the night.
Hello. You came from Korea.
- You're from Garak-dong.
- Nice to see you.
Isn't it hot?
I didn't know it would be this hot.
Have a great trip.
I just landed.
This is why they call it "Da Nang of Gyeonggi Province."
(Currency Exchange)
It's my first time exchanging money locally.
Hello. Goodness, you speak Korean?
Hello.
(There's no need to worry about exchanging money locally.)
(Exchanging money, done)
First,
I use the taxi application whenever I'm in Vietnam.
Grab is hassle-free.
(Travel Tip for Moo Friends)
There's no overpricing.
(The roads in Vietnam are narrow and packed with motorcycles.)
It shows you the path you're on.
(So taking a taxi is a convenient way to travel.)
I'm craving pho.
I want to sit on a tiny stool at a local stall and eat pho.
(At Hyun Moo's age, you crave broth.)
That's my taxi.
The plate is 432002.5. This is the one.
(Hyun Moo hasn't eaten for many hours.)
Excuse me.
Can you introduce me to the best restaurant?
Your best restaurant.
Delicious restaurant.
Your...
(It seems like he got it.)
(Speaking Vietnamese)
- Jjao eh?
Jjao eh-k.
Okay.
(Hyun Moo doesn't speak any Vietnamese.)
Jjao eh unnie?
Noodles?
Noodles? Best?
(Is it a noodle restaurant beloved by locals?)
(Anxious)
(They head to the restaurant recommended by the driver.)
I haven't had Vietnamese food in so long.
This is what I love to do these days.
When I get into a taxi, I ask the driver for a restaurant.
The taxi drivers know...
the best local restaurants.
(The taxi drivers know the best local restaurants.)
Recently, this happened. There were two ramen places...
with slightly different names. They were both old restaurants.
(Tourists)
All the tourists were going to this ramen place.
But the taxi driver told me,
"That place is good too,"
"but I go to this ramen place."
So I went to this place.
It was good.
And there were no tourists.
Researching where everyone goes,
checking the rating on Google,
and deciding where to go ahead of time...
lowers the chance of failure, but it takes the fun away.
It's the most fun when you just wing it.
I think any of these places would be good.
This is what's good about Asia.
All the shops are open until late.
Every shop is open, and they have outdoor seats.
Gosh, nobody sleeps.
(It's almost midnight, but Da Nang is wide-awake.)
I guess we're here.
(Is this the local hot spot?)
(Trust me.)
Thank you.
It must be breezy here.
(He cautiously steps into the unfamiliar restaurant.)
There's no Korean.
(The “no Koreans” criterion: passed)
Goodness.
I love this stool.
Squatting down on a stool you'd see at a public bathhouse...
It puts strain on your hip joints, but you still sit there and eat.
(The Taxi Driver's Local Restaurant Recommendation)
(Da Nang International Restaurant)
(Local Time: 11:15pm)
Look at those earthen pots.
(There is a mysterious pile of earthen pots.)
Hello.
The food the lady is eating. What is that?
The bread?
No, the pot.
She's eating something. The guest.
(What is she eating?)
It's braised meat.
- Braised meat?
- Frog.
Frog? No.
- No frog?
- No frog.
They are all frogs.
(The taxi driver recommended a frog restaurant.)
What?
They are all frogs.
(Yes, it's me.)
(Vietnam’s ultimate rice companion)
(Chao Ech: Frog body and leg braised in spicy sauce)
(It means "frog porridge" when translated literally,)
(but white porridge is served separately with the braised frog.)
(It's a popular restorative dish for the heat-weary body and soul.)
It's a restorative dish.
That's why Vietnamese eat frogs often.
Children often eat frog porridge, too.
(It's the popular restorative dish for people of all generations.)
(It's also the best night snack beloved by the Vietnamese.)
(Day and night, this comfort food satisfies everyone's hunger.)
(It's my first time to have a Korean customer.)
Gosh, frog!
(The 1st Korean customer is agonized.)
Gosh, frog. No.
(I wish my past self would've kept quiet.)
(Hyun Moo is thrilled to try frog.)
I should try the frog.
Frog dishes are all they serve.
They must specialise in frog dishes.
(There are only frogs)
Let's give it a try.
Hello.
I will try the frog.
What's the best here?
- Bestseller?
- Yes, a bestseller.
Claypot frog.
Is it spicy? I like spicy food.
- Okay.
- Spicy, okay?
- Spicy, okay.
Two frogs? Or one frog?
One frog. Noodles.
- And one beer?
- One beer.
Okay.
Thank you.
(I will have faith in the driver.)
(Frog)
(Special soy sauce)
(Spicy chilli sauce)
(Scallions)
(Vietnamese braised frog)
(A family enters the restaurant.)
(Envious)
(Gosh)
So this is the frog.
(Hyun Moo is proud of himself for taking on a new challenge.)
(The first meal in Vietnam, featuring frog)
(First encounter with the braised frog)
Gosh, the leg is...
(Dear Moo Friends, is frog going too far?)
(Hyun Moo is agonized.)
(It's good. Why isn't he eating it?)
(Intimidated)
(Intimidated again)
(He's finally eating it.)
It's good.
It actually tastes like chicken.
It's the thigh. Yes!
(He’s discovered just how tasty frog can be.)
The thigh meat is good.
It's the shape of the frog that makes it tough.
It tastes perfectly good. It doesn't have any unpleasant smell.
(He slowly immerses in the local culture.)
Frog is all right.
This is my first frog.
(Summer of 2026, he tastes his first-ever frog.)
The beer is great.
(It's an unfamiliar place...)
(he randomly discovered.)
(Travel always puts the mind at ease.)
So these are the noodles.
Am I supposed to dip it in the sauce?
Is it like tsukemen?
(Is it eaten like tsukemen?)
(Checking other people)
(Hyun Moo looks around,)
(but he's the only one who ordered noodles.)
(He chucks them into the sauce.)
Is this the right way?
(Anxious)
Excuse me.
Hello.
Is this the right way of eating?
- This is my first time.
- Yes.
- Do I put the noodles in here?
- Okay.
Right?
- Well...
- Yes?
Put the noodles inside.
Put the noodles inside? Here?
- Mix the...
- Mix them and eat?
Yes.
(The beloved local delicacy: Braised frog and noodles)
Do you like this dish?
- Yes, I like it.
- Frog?
(He sits down.)
This food is very delicious.
- Delicious?
- Delicious.
I usually come here.
- With your family.
- With my family.
You come here and...
You don't eat chicken or beef. You only eat frog?
- Yes.
- Really?
I see.
- Okay.
He is sitting too close.
- Nice to meet you.
- Okay. Thank you.
(People in Da Nang are very kind.)
Oh?
What is that?
This is my family.
No, I mean...
It's fried rice with frog.
It's called com chay in Vietnamese.
- Com chay?
Com chay.
(The frog dish can be enjoyed in a variety of ways.)
(Scorched rice and braise frog is a dish with a nice crunch.)
(Hot porridge and braised frog is the popular restorative dish.)
(Thick noodles and braised frog is a filling meal.)
(The Vietnamese enjoy frog in many ways.)
Okay. Thank you.
You're welcome.
So this is the right way to eat it.
It tastes quite good.
I've never eaten something like this before.
(Hyun Moo seems to like it.)
This is my first time to eat something like this.
It's my first time eating braised meat in Vietnam.
This is tasty.
You're a naughty boy, aren't you?
(He's got a mischievous little frog face.)
(He's been running around, not eating.)
(It looks good, doesn't it? Here.)
(I don't want to eat.)
(I'm going to play!)
(Gosh, this boy.)
(Every child in the world...)
(wants to play and not eat.)
(Acting cute)
He's a good dad.
That's why he's married.
He's a good man.
(Dad, have some water.)
(Big uncle's smile)
(Give me the delivery charge.)
(Here you go.)
I will give you some too. Here.
(Here)
Okay.
So kind.
I should go now.
- How much is it?
- It's 3.5 dollars.
- It's 3.5.
Yes.
If I remove zero from it, that becomes...
Is it just 3.5 dollars?
(He paid 3.5 dollars for braised pork, noodles, and beer.)
Here.
(The big uncle returns the favour.)
Thank you.
Bye.
Thank you. Bye.
You won't remember this day.
Bye, you.
Gosh, I'm full.
(It was my first time trying frog, but it tasted nice and familiar.)
(Next time, I will make sure to try the frog porridge.)
I booked a hotel, so I should head there now.
The time is...
It's already past midnight here.
It's 2am in Korea.
Look at the night market.
When do these night markets close?
(The night streets of Da Nang are still brightly lit.)
Should I drop by?
(The locals make him drop by.)
Right. This is the vibe I wanted.
(People enjoy the night at the brightly lit streets.)
Yes, I wanted this bustling vibe.
(He trusts his instinct and gets off the car.)
Oh, yes. I love it.
(Are there any Koreans?)
Fried rice.
(Locals)
It's nice.
There are no Koreans.
(He found the local night market with no Korean tourists.)
(Groaning)
Goodness.
Gosh, it's killing me.
(The Taxi Driver's Restaurant Recommendation)
(Night Market)
I should eat something with broth.
(Looking)
(Around)
(Nobody recognises Hyun Moo.)
Are they not going to give me the menu? Here it is.
It's all written in Vietnamese.
(Blue paper and black writings are what he sees.)
This shows that Koreans don't come here.
(There's no English either on the menu.)
There's no English on the menu.
(He ends up using the translating app.)
(Translated)
"The name of this place is 'Fat Hyo Sung.'"
(The name of the place is Fat Hyo Sung.)
The first dishes on the menu are sweet and sour pork,
false, frog chicken wing...
What does this mean?
(The translation quality is poor.)
- Do you have the English menu?
- No.
(I see.)
(He picks up the translating app again.)
Okay?
(Do you have the pho with broth?)
Quán không có bán phở
"I don't sell it."
No pho.
(We don't have pho.)
Okay.
What's the bestselling dish?
Xiên nướng.
Skewers.
(Char-grilled skewers)
(Everyone is holding a skewer.)
Why is nobody selling pho?
(It's hard to eat pho.)
Okay. Tiger beer.
Gosh, it's lukewarm.
Okay. I got ice.
Ice.
(The room temperature beer is served with ice.)
(Ice and beer)
(200% refreshed.)
(Enjoying the night breeze, he relaxedly sips the beer.)
It's fascinating.
They bring their kids. They are very family-oriented.
They could leave the kids home...
and come out by themselves.
They are here together, enjoying the night snacks.
(They enjoy the night outing with the family.)
And the dads are all young.
(Feeling sad)
(We must be willing to let go of the life we planned...)
(in order to make room for the real life...)
(awaiting us.)
(The char-grilled skewers are served.)
Thank you.
(Satisfied)
It will go perfectly with beer.
(Dear Moo Friends, can you smell the aroma?)
(I want to go!)
It smells smoky.
It tastes smoky. It's got that char-grilled smell.
(The juicy chicken is infused with the smoky aroma.)
It's nicely sweet.
It pairs perfectly with beer.
When it comes to Vietnam,
street food beats hotel room service.
Hello?
- Hyun Moo.
- Are you coming?
I just landed.
Where are you?
I just landed at the airport.
Where should we go?
I will send you the address.
Call a taxi on Grab...
and ask the driver to come here.
- Okay.
- Bye.
I wouldn't let my buddy...
eat just anything.
Excuse me.
(Additional order!)
(He orders fried bitter melon and egg and beef tendon stir-fry...)
(for his mysterious friend.)
Okay.
(Who's coming to meet Hyun Moo?)
When I was a broadcaster,
he was a regular guest to "Star Golden Bell."
He's popular, good-looking,
a great dancer and singer,
and he's goofy.
(Several hours ago at Incheon International Airport)
I'm a minimalist,
so I don't like packing a lot.
(Minimal travel buddy, Lee Joon)
There's this excitement you feel before you fly.
It's the airport smell.
I feel like a star.
(I feel like a star.)
(The day of Lee Joon's pre-show interview)
What's this show all about?
(3 days before the shoot)
(What's Lee Joon's travel style?)
I often travel virtually.
I normally plan my days.
But the only time I don't plan...
is when I travel.
When I travel with my friends or my partner,
we often get into an argument.
So I am a little traumatized about travelling.
I have mild PTSD.
So if I were to travel,
I want my travel companion to be happy.
That's the most important thing.
I want to...
experience the local culture...
and learn about the country.
The more local it is, the more fun it is.
I want a memorable trip.
(Hyun Moo's travel buddy, Lee Joon appears.)
I don't see him. Where is he?
(He spots Hyun Moo.)
(Hyun Moo spots him too.)
(Just looking at each other makes them burst out laughing.)
It's strange to see you here.
Don't I look like a middle-aged Vietnamese man?
- Have a seat.
- You blend in perfectly.
- I had a hard time finding you.
- You had a hard time?
Then I looked for someone sitting alone.
- I was on the way to the hotel.
- Right.
But Vietnam is known for its night markets, you know.
On the way to the hotel, this place caught my attention.
You didn't do much then.
No, I didn't. I just got here as well.
(Touching)
What?
I lost a lot of weight.
- I lost some weight.
- You became fitter.
I actually lost some weight.
I feel like you bulked up.
Really? I actually lost some weight.
Hey, what?
- What?
- Is this all you came with?
- Yes.
- What about a suitcase?
I brought this one bag here.
You're like Kian84.
(It's right here.)
- But I...
- Yes?
brought quite a lot of clothes.
What's in here?
- Well...
- Do a "What's in My Bag?"
There's really not much in here.
Socks. Underwear.
(Joon's bag for a 4-day trip, 1. Socks and underwear)
Underwear. Hold on.
- I wear something like this too.
- It has a naked feel.
- It really does.
- You know what I mean, right?
- Seamless.
- Then this T-shirt.
- I brought a new one.
- You're right, it's new.
I brought three of the same ones.
What's the difference between each of these?
This makes things so easy.
You don't have to think about what to wear the next day.
- Did you not bring pants?
- Just this pair.
Because...
With pants...
Doesn't it feel icky?
My lower body doesn't sweat much.
- My lower body...
- It's not like mine does.
- It just feels icky.
- It doesn't.
I just have to feel clean when I go to bed.
My suitcase is this big.
It's full of clothes. I can't stand feeling icky.
When I wear something once, I put it away...
and wear something new.
I'll show you. My lower body really doesn't sweat.
(Okay, sure...)
Anyway, welcome.
(Finally having a welcome drink with his travel buddy)
Eat.
This is beef tendon stir-fry.
(Hyun Moo's recommendation, Beef tendon stir-fry)
This is nice.
(Already enjoying the local flavours)
Good.
This is cilantro. Do you like cilantro?
I do. Do you?
I'm okay with it.
I eat it a lot.
(They have similar tastes in underwear and food.)
(Joon takes a bite.)
(Hyun Moo takes a bite.)
- Have you been to Da Nang?
- No.
- Is this your first time?
- Yes. Have you been here before?
A long time ago. Five years ago. Or was it six?
Usually, for this kind of program,
I usually study about Da Nang in advance.
Because I need to be the guide.
But I didn't study at all this time.
- I see.
- We'll go with the flow.
I studied a bit on the way here on the plane.
Say one, two, three, four. What is this?
Oh, my... That!
Oh, my... That! That's a cockroach.
We can't do this. Hold on.
(Hyun Moo is frozen in place.)
Those cockroaches can fly.
Oh, wait. Oh, gosh.
Wait. This is...
Why are we the only ones who are scared?
Exactly. This is a bit...
Oh, gosh. It really does fly around too much.
(What's wrong with them?)
- Oh, gosh... But...
- It's really fat.
- It wasn't here when I was alone.
- Right.
It came because you smell.
What?
Because you don't wash your clothes.
This is a new shirt.
I don't think either of us are fit for this sort of travel.
Will we be okay?
How do you like to travel?
But these trips are very memorable.
I really remember the time I went to the jungle.
It has stayed with me as such a good memory.
What was that? You did that on purpose, didn't you?
- Hyun Moo.
- Don't do it.
(Trying not to laugh)
I'm not lying. It came this close to your head.
(It's been a while, but they're already so much alike.)
Let's eat while standing.
(Extraordinary measures)
(This 3-night, 4-day trip in Vietnam will be full of...)
(their fantastic chemistry...)
(that goes beyond bromance.)
(Like, comment, subscribe, and click the notification button.)
(Please stay tuned.)
But once you arrive, you enjoy it, right?
- So much.
- Right?
I love it.
Have you heard of the expression, "Da Nang City, Gyeonggi Province?"
Oh, it's very famous.
Because so many people come here.
I'm planning to go to places that not even those Gyeonggi people,
those Korean people go.
- Doesn't that sound fun?
- It does.
I like things like that.
Let's explore new places.
Even this place doesn't have any Korean people.
- It doesn't.
- Not at all.
Not one.
Seriously.
It left.
Really?
- Tell me what you want to do, - Okay.
and I'll reflect that in our plans.
Can I go work out?
(Joon wants to work out.)
We don't have to work out with the same intensity, right?
Of course.
I like getting massages.
- Oh, massages. I also...
- You don't like them, do you?
I don't really have things...
I particularly dislike.
I'm also good at adjusting to others.
Let's each choose one thing we want to do, then.
That sounds great.
(Drinking to their deal)
Let's go to our lodging.
Let's go.
I'm so full. I ate too much.
Wait. It's 280...
Take a zero off from 280,000 dong.
Then it's 28,000 right?
It's 14 dollars.
It's 16.1 dollars.
- Okay, 16.1 dollars.
That's pretty good. For 16.1 dollars...
Here.
Chào anh.
- What?
- Chào anh.
What is chào anh?
It's how you say "Thank you" to a man older than you.
- Chào anh?
- Yes.
- Like, "Aing?" - Like that.
Chào anh.
And to someone younger, "chào em."
So to that person, "chào anh?"
- Should we try saying it?
- He could be younger than you.
Chào anh.
(Bowing)
Chào em.
It worked.
I'm glad I studied.
Chào anh.
- Chào anh.
(Joon and I met for the first time in a while at a local market.)
(It's been a long time, but we still make a good team.)
(I'm already excited about this trip.)
This is fun.
Let's go. It's so hot.
Nobody's going to sleep.
(The night in Da Nang is still hot.)
(They head back to their lodging to rest up for the remaining trip.)
When we were on "Star Golden Bell" together,
we went to the same hair salon.
- Your stylist was Ga Ho, right?
- Ga Ho.
Right? Do you remember?
I remember this.
"Joon, I go to the same hair salon as you."
(Joon clearly remembers Hyun Moo talking to him for the first time.)
I wanted to become close to you.
Right. I remember that.
I didn't have celebrities I could get close to.
I was afraid of everyone.
Now that I think about it,
I was a newbie,
and you were a broadcaster.
That's so interesting, now that I think about it.
(After a long time, they've become travel buddies.)
Seriously.
At every shoot, you tried to really kill it.
(After a while of sharing memories from 16 years ago)
(Looking around)
Is this our lodging?
There's nothing here.
It feels like a horror movie.
Oh, my. It's 2am.
(It's past 2am. The road is eerie, with no lights or people.)
This is a safe area, right?
(Worried, Where is our lodging?)
(They've arrived?)
Let's get off. Oh, gosh.
- Oh, gosh.
Oh, gosh.
Where are we?
We have to go this way.
Let's see...
It's this way.
(They carefully slow the map.)
You're right.
It is a nice place,
but it looks scary at night.
And hotels are cheaper when you go on the day of.
On the day of.
(Surprised)
(Booking a hotel without Koreans)
Oh, this is scary.
This is too much like "R-Point."
(It looks like a scene from a horror movie.)
(Pitch-black darkness)
(A road with a peculiar atmosphere)
Oh, that really scared me.
Oh, my. Oh, I'm scared.
(Is this the right way?)
Oh, what is this? This is scary.
(Hyun Moo received a message at this late hour?)
(A creepy-feeling voice message)
What is this? It's like the movie, "The Medium".
"Why aren't you here yet?"
"We waited so long..."
- "to go eat..." - Why aren't you here yet?
We waited so long...
to go eat.
Oh, they waited for so long. I think we need to hurry.
They're not explaining how to get there.
They're explaining their feelings...
- They're very angry.
- Wait... I think they're angry.
I'm glad it wasn't anything about ghosts or something.
I think it's that one up there, not this one.
- Isn't it that man?
- Is that it?
They're waiting to eat with us.
This is it.
(Impressed)
Hello.
It's very nice.
(Outdoor market)
(Lodging)
(Checking the voice message just in case)
- You?
- Yes.
Sorry.
They haven't eaten. I feel bad.
(Worried)
Shall we eat?
(Joon tries speaking Korean in the middle of Da Nang.)
The room is so nice.
Okay.
Oh, it's nice and cool.
(Impressed as soon as they open the door)
This is amazing!
It's pretty nice, right?
What is this here? Is this a pool?
- It's a pool.
- We have a pool!
A pool villa!
Oh, my. This is nice.
Amazing.
(Let's us show you around this luxury pool villa.)
People usually think of resorts or hotels when it comes to Da Nang.
We have a big dining room here.
We have a pool outside. We have a kitchen.
And there's also a room here.
- There's a room on the first floor?
- There is.
Oh, my. What is this?
(The 1st-floor room has a huge bed and floor-to-ceiling windows.)
The pool is right there. You can just jump right in.
It's so clean.
(You can just open up the curtains and jump right into the pool.)
(1st floor, front floor, sofa, dining room, bedroom, pool)
Are there many rooms upstairs too?
Let's check it out.
(The 2nd floor seems cosy.)
Okay.
Oh, my. They're all main rooms.
It's so spacious.
They're all main rooms.
Several people could stay here.
They all have TVs, double beds, and showers.
(2nd floor, stairs, bathroom, room 1, room 2, room 3, terrace)
What? There's even a third floor?
No way. Oh, my. It's even bigger.
(On the 3rd floor is the biggest room!)
Five couples could stay here together.
Ten people could stay here.
(5 rooms, private showers, a laundry room, and a pool!)
(A 3-story luxury villa)
- How much?
- How much was it?
It was 300 dollars.
(The 3-story villa is only 300 dollars for 1 night.)
That's so cheap.
If I knew it was this big,
I would've brought more people.
People could've slept upstairs. It would've been so much fun.
Anyway, it's 2:30am already.
- It's very late.
- Yes, let's go to bed.
Let's wash up and go to bed.
Tell me if there's something you want to do tomorrow.
I'll do some research in bed.
Well, then. Goodnight.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
This feels like real travelling, with separate rooms and all.
(The first night of the Da Nang trip comes to an end.)
(The sun rises with energy on the second morning.)
(The scenery around their lodging they couldn't see yesterday)
(A cosy place to rest)
- To the sky.
- Goodness.
Oh, hold on.
Oh, gosh! That hurts.
Push your butt up to the sky. Push, push.
As fast as you can. This is no joke, right?
Keep going. Quickly.
Higher up to the sky.
- To the sky. Oh, hold on.
- Oh, gosh!
(Hyun Moo finally exploded.)
- Oh, that hurts.
- That's so irritating.
- It is, right?
I was feeling so good after washing up.
(Exploding with irritation)
It's for your energy.
The main reason I exercise is energy.
My energy levels are very different when I exercise and when I don't.
Don't use momentum. Go slowly.
(Charging up on energy with morning lunges)
Slowly.
We did lunges together.
I was very touched by that.
I was very thankful that you did it with me.
- People normally don't do that.
- Oh, really?
People who don't work out...
- don't understand.
- Oh, that's why my thighs...
- are dead right now.
- Yes.
(If Joon is happy, Hyun Moo is happy too.)
(Feels like 37°C)
(Their morning in Da Nang starts with scorching heat.)
It's such a beautiful place. It was so scary at night.
It's not scary at all. Is this the taxi we called?
This one.
(The taxi they called in advance is here.)
- Hello.
This is nice.
Let's eat and think about what to do.
Okay.
(Day 2 of their trip in Da Nang)
This is nice.
I'm feeling great.
So pretty.
It's similar to the Han River.
It was so scary yesterday, but it's a very beautiful place.
Oh, this is what it looked like.
(They finally get to see the beautiful scenery.)
Oh, it's the ocean.
This place was getting popular was I came here 5 or 6 years ago.
There were lots of Korean people back then too.
I was eating the hotel breakfast, and 80 percent were Korean people.
Is the goal of the trip not to run into Korean people?
Avoid Korean people.
(The mission for the "Da Nang Trip," Avoid Korean people.)
Da Nang has so many attractive places,
but we always to go the same places.
We're going to a place that a stranger recommended yesterday.
This is fun.
I'm here for travel, right?
So can you recommend my breakfast for tomorrow morning?
- So many local people...
- Yes.
- go there. Mì Quảng.
- Mì Quảng.
We call it Mì Quảng.
(This is Mì Quảng.)
I looked it up, and it has a high rating.
This is an unexpected find.
People who always plan ahead...
- can't enjoy this happiness.
- Right.
Hyun Moo. I'm normally a planner.
I always plan ahead for everything, but I change when I travel.
- There we go.
- I change completely.
Because work is already stressful. If you plan your travels too...
Life isn't all about completing missions.
We really get along well.
I often say, "If not, that's fine."
I'm just like that too.
(They even hold the handles in the same way too.)
This is so fascinating.
This is nice.
(Chapter one, In search of the local-recommended Mì Quảng)
(They arrived at their destination.)
- Bye-bye.
There's no traffic light.
(A crosswalk without a traffic light)
(Motorcycles and cars speed by.)
You just have to cross in Vietnam.
(Is this okay?)
- We just cross?
- Of course.
- Right, there's no traffic light.
- If you want to cross, you cross.
- Oh, you just go...
- Whoever wants to go, goes.
(Powering through the crosswalk with no traffic light)
- There we go.
- They're driving around us.
- Of course.
We're just going straight, and they're driving around us.
Think of being a fish in water.
You have to blend in.
They don't even honk.
(A travel tip for our Moo friend: In Vietnam, motorcycles and cars...)
(drive around people who are crossing the street.)
(A honk means, "I'm driving by.")
I love it. These sorts of places have amazing coffee.
I love this place.
(A cafe in an alley)
This place is really my style.
See you.
(Have a fun trip.)
- Oh, my.
- Oh, this is it. Stand there.
This is...
We have to get a picture here.
(A hidden cosy alley in the middle of the busy city)
Don't stand there like a fool. Be natural.
(Hyun Moo gets his camera out.)
Look.
(We are trailblazers. Starting Monday, September 20)
Are you good at taking pictures?
You're a bit stiff. This is how you do it. Like this.
(Looking into the distance)
(Serious)
You're a good photographer. Oh, my.
- I made you look tall.
- Why are you so good?
If you learn...
I learned...
How did you learn?
Like...
What?
You can't help but get good if you date a lot.
(Hyun Moo seems to have understood right away...)
That's why I was scolded.
After being scolded a few times, you improve right away.
This place...
- This place is great too.
- This place is nice too.
This place is so pretty.
It's so pretty.
I love this.
(A street lined with cafes full of local vibes)
Oh, look at this place.
Oh, we have to go this way.
We're a minute away.
- Yes, a minute.
- A minute away.
(It's drizzling, but it's still nice to walk around the neighbourhood.)
- I think this is it.
- Right?
I think we just have to turn around here.
Turn and go right.
We're almost there.
- Oh, yes...
- This is it. Mỳ Quảng.
Wait.
Mỳ Quảng. Right?
- Yes.
- Mỳ Quảng.
That's it.
(You can tell it's a local favourite just from the sign.)
This is it. Here we go.
(They arrived at the restaurant recommended by a local.)
(Lodging)
(Mì Quảng restaurant)
That lady must be a good cook.
Her hair is coloured.
This is it.
This is really nice.
(Hyun Moo trusts food cooked by ladies with coloured hair.)
This really feels like a home.
It looks like a house inside.
- It really is.
- Yes, it looks like a house.
It's a living room.
(It's currently 9:24am. The regulars are already here.)
(It feels like you're over at a Vietnamese friend's house.)
(What food will they get to eat in this approachable place?)
Not many people live around this area,
and not many tourists either.
We mostly get regulars.
(The restaurant already busy with regulars.)
(Mì Quảng is tasty!)
- Oh, right away...
- Of course.
(They are served cilantro as soon as they sit down.)
(Cilantro gives Vietnamese dishes that full aroma.)
(Like Korean leafy greens, there are many types of cilantro.)
(Cilantro holds the same position kimchi does in Korea.)
Let's see.
That man recommended...
to eat Mì Quảng at Mỳ Quảng.
(Make sure to eat Mì Quảng at this place.)
This place is called Mỳ Quảng,
- and we have to eat Mì Quảng here.
- Mì Quảng?
He also told me to eat Mì Hải Sản.
- Mì Hải Sản?
- Mì Hải Sản.
(Today's breakfast is Mì Quảng and Mì Hải Sản.)
Mì Quảng?
(She didn't hear him.)
(They're just trying to order, and they're already struggling.)
Mì Quảng?
- Mì Quảng?
Mì Hải Sản?
Mì Quảng?
Mì Quảng with shrimp, meat, and eggs?
Yes. One.
Mì Hải Sản...
(Don't go.)
(Is this right?)
(Nodding?)
Mì Quảng...
(They're not sure if they ordered correctly.)
- Our communication...
- We can't...
communicate with them at all.
(We can't communicate with them at all.)
Oh, goodness.
(The downside of local spots, Communication isn't smooth.)
We could really get to know this country...
- if we spoke the language.
- Seriously.
- They're kind of like Koreans.
- They are. Their food too.
Is that Mì Quảng back there?
- Mì Quảng?
- It's Mì Quảng.
- He says it's Mì Quảng.
- He says it is.
- Mì Quảng.
That... Mì Quảng. This one.
- Mì Quảng?
- Yes.
Oh, Mì Quảng. This one.
(They really want to eat Mì Quảng.)
We want this one here. Mì Quảng.
(All they know how to say is Mì Quảng.)
- Okay. Mì Quảng.
- Mì Quảng
Mì Quảng...
(Curious what Mì Quảng is like)
Okay. Mì Quảng is a saucy rice noodle dish...
that's popular in Tỉnh Quảng Nam and Da Nang,
the central region of Vietnam.
Mì Quảng is a famous local dish from Vietnam's central region.
Unlike regular rice noodles, Mì Quảng doesn't have much broth.
It's made with deep rich bone broth, boiled for a long time.
Each restaurant uses its own style and spices.
It's eaten with various toppings,
such as shrimp, pork, chicken, and beef.
(Mì Quảng, a popular Da Nang breakfast dish...)
(with wide noodles and simmered-down soup)
- Oh, Mì Quảng?
- Mì Quảng. Hải Sản.
- Hải Sản.
Seafood.
(Mì Hải Sản, Meaning "seafood noodle dish" in Vietnamese)
(Stir-fried, served with broth, it's enjoyed in various ways.)
- Here's the Mì Quảng.
- Mì Quảng?
Mine has more seafood in it.
- Do you want to eat this?
- It doesn't matter to me.
- This looks good.
I like that it's served so quickly.
(Mì Hải Sản, Mì Quảng)
(Their first breakfast in Da Nang, 200 percent local-style)
Apparently, they also put frogs in here.
- Really?
- I think they love frogs here.
I mean, it's mostly protein.
Right.
(Getting excited while mixing the Mì Quảng)
I've never seen something like this before.
Is this a type of fish?
Oh, fish.
(The flavour makes him nod.)
(Highly satisfied)
It's clean-tasting.
It's nice and salty.
(The rich meat broth with the light shrimp flavour...)
(makes a perfect soup to mix the wide noodles into.)
(Joon starts his eating show.)
I like it. It's good.
(Furrowing his eyebrows from satisfaction)
It's good.
What? Rice puffs?
Oh, I see.
Okay. I saw they eat it this way.
(Local style, A snack to eat with Mì Quảng)
- Okay. I see.
- Okay.
- Chào em.
- Chào anh.
(Bánh tráng mè, A nutty and crunchy rice cracker to eat with Mì Quảng)
Put some of this.
Vietnam really is a great place to come and eat.
(Day 2 in Da Nang, He has fallen in love with Vietnamese food.)
I think this dish would be popular in Korea. Don't you think?
- Definitely.
- Just as it is.
It's not too unfamiliar.
Right.
(Crunchy)
(Hyun Moo adds a spoonful of spice.)
- It's perfect right now.
- I like spicy food.
If you can't handle spice, you can't eat this.
I can handle spice. I like spicy food.
(Hyun Moo really likes the spicy sauce.)
This is sweet chilli, and this is chilli.
Oh, it's good.
I want to tell that dad yesterday...
(Thank you.)
- Should I try this?
- This?
(Curious about the spicy sauce after seeing Hyun Moo's reaction)
It might be too spicy for you. Are you sure?
Yes, I do like spicy food.
I can really handle spice,
but my stomach doesn't like it.
It's good, right? It's so good.
- I like it.
- Yes.
This is tasty.
(Very satisfied)
It's nice and warm too. It's perfect.
This is a spicy flavour that Korean people like.
- Right.
- It's not too strong.
It's spicy in a tasty way.
- Right?
- Yes.
I like cilantro.
Oh, Hyun Moo. This is...
- a bit too much.
- What?
Why are you adding so much?
(There's more cilantro than noodles.)
I usually add this much.
I even eat the roots.
- Really?
- Look.
(Even the locals are fascinated.)
- Cilantro...
- Yes?
- actually helps with digestion.
I see.
(Copying Hyun Moo and adding lots of cilantro)
I don't eat it for no reason.
- I want to try it like you.
- It's tasty.
- Let's try everything.
- Like this?
(Cilantro party)
(Moved)
It's pretty nice.
(It's day two of the trip, and they're already growing close.)
Except for the market yesterday,
this is our first real meal here.
- It's delicious.
- I like this place much better.
This place is really nice.
Actually, yesterday, the man...
said it was a thicker soup.
That's not really my style. I'm not a saucy noodle guy.
I like drinking lots of broth.
But this is making me forget the rice noodles I normally like.
These are the most unique and delicious rice noodles...
I think I've ever tried.
Getting recommendations from locals...
is always the best.
You can't search this place from Korea.
Exactly.
(Agreed)
(They finished eating at the same time.)
You eat at a similar speed as me.
That's interesting.
- I knock things back quickly.
- I do too.
That's so interesting. We finished at the same time.
(They're even similar on how fast they eat.)
I've never experienced this before.
- Oh, my. That's funny.
- I eat fast.
Everything is perfect so far.
And we didn't plan anything.
This is a nice place. I'm going to save it.
(Their first breakfast in Da Nang was a success.)
- What should we do now?
- What should we do?
Do you want to go there? That coffee place we saw earlier?
- Sure.
- For a dessert?
We have to have dessert. Do you remember where it was?
- I know where it is.
- I'm bad with directions.
How much is it?
It's 60,000 dong. Take off a zero...
- So 6,000, then it's 3 - It's only 3 dollars.
(One bowl of Mì Quảng, 25,000 dong, One bowl of Mì Hải Sản, 35,000 dong)
That's amazing!
It's three dollars for two?
It's really cheap.
(They're once again surprised by how cheap things are in Vietnam.)
Goodness.
How nice.
(Vietnamese noodles. I only thought of pho,)
(so it was a pleasant surprise.)
(Mì Quảng is a funny name, but it tastes amazing.)
These are all residential houses.
They're all residential houses. Look.
Since it's a hot day,
they came out for a bit to rest in between work.
(To escape the intense heat,)
The weather here makes you feel sluggish.
(a culture of taking a midday break emerged.)
It's so hot.
You remember the coffee place we saw earlier, right?
I do. We'll take a left here.
It's right there.
(Following the same route they took to the restaurant)
This is life.
Getting a cup of coffee while leaning on the wall.
(Vietnam's beloved sidewalk cafe culture)
It's a long cafe.
- Right.
- It's attached.
This would be so nice because of the nice sun.
This is really magical.
- Hi.
The menu...
I'll get orange juice.
- What?
- I can't take caffeine.
You're getting juice at a cafe?
I usually do that.
(The owner recommends refreshing lemon juice)
What would you like? Lemon?
Yes.
- Lemon?
- Lemon.
Lemon juice, and for me...
- Bạc xỉu.
- Okay.
Bạc xỉu.
Bạc xỉu...
is Vietnamese white coffee. That's Bạc xỉu.
- It's the traditional coffee.
- Yes.
(Vietnam's signature sweet coffee with condensed milk and milk)
Let's drink a cup of coffee...
and decide what to do today.
They're bringing it to us.
- Chào.
- Chào anh.
(Greeting for the nth time)
- Lemon.
- Lemon juice?
- Trà đá.
- Trà đá?
Try it.
(It's not salty.)
Mine?
Here?
- Together? Okay.
- Do we mix them?
Mix.
No. Drink them separately.
Drink this,
and then drink this.
(A refreshing tea consumed almost like water in Vietnam)
(It is often served with coffee as a palate cleanser.)
(There's trà đá here and there.)
I need to drink all of them.
What does it matter?
- Right.
- That doesn't matter.
It's really tasty.
This is really good.
It's just what I like.
(Frowning)
- Is it sour?
- It's sour.
- I love it.
- You like healthy things.
(I like it.)
(He tries to shake off the taste with bạc xỉu.)
Right.
(Taking a relaxing sip with nothing on their minds)
The sound of motorcycles...
(They're getting familiar with the streets of Da Nang.)
(They've blended naturally into the local scenery.)
(Hyun Moo and Joon also take some rest.)
I always drink coffee when I come to Vietnam.
Vietnamese coffee...
tastes good in Vietnam.
- Really?
- We had it in Korea as well.
- It didn't taste the same?
- It didn't.
- I wonder why.
- You need to drink it...
in this kind of vibe.
On a hot day.
I really love it here.
(I really love it here.)
(I've got to take pictures of this place.)
(Hold on)
My phone is gone!
- Where's my phone?
- What are you talking about?
Seriously. I'm serious.
- What?
- Did you leave it behind?
Should I call your phone?
(At the Mì Quảng place?)
(Or at their accommodation?)
I never lose things.
(Hyun Moo tries calling his phone.)
You remember where it was, right?
Run.
- Run.
- Let me get one more sip.
It's right here!
(Suddenly feeling happy)
(It was right under his nose.)
(The site of the incident)
(Joon is very clumsy.)
I'm not lying.
I had no idea.
(Lifespan minus 10)
I just called. Why didn't it ring?
It's on silent mode.
How would you find it when it's on silent mode?
I never lose things.
I'm exhausted.
Already?
- It's 10:20am.
- I'm sleepy.
What do you want to do?
Actually,
there's a place I was really curious about.
About 9 out of 10 people...
who come to Da Nang...
go to My Khe Beach.
(My Khe Beach)
It's a long beach.
If you go...
about five minutes away from My Khe Beach,
there's a beach called...
We can look for this there.
The yellow tree.
Really?
You rarely find Korean people there.
It's a hidden gem.
(A hidden beach in Da Nang with no Korean people)
(A different side of Da Nang awaits just around the corner.)
(There's a beach in this mysterious jungle?)
(Are you intruders?)
(Even the wild animals are wary of outsiders.)
(A beach only known to locals)
(Even if they get soaking wet,)
(they're just happy.)
(A beach only the locals used to enjoy)
Coconut juice?
(In search of a hidden gem of a getaway)
It was good.
I'm full.
- It's huge.
- It's amazing.
- Han River.
- Han.
- Han River?
- Han River.
Really? The size of it is also similar to ours.
It's the Dragon Bridge.
(A river that begins in Quảng Nam, flows through Da Nang,)
(and empties into the South China Sea)
Is this like the Hannam Bridge in Korea?
- Right.
- It's just the same.
(A giant dragon stretches along the river.)
(The Dragon Bridge, a landmark in Da Nang)
(A fire show that lights up the nights of Da Nang)
(They head east toward the sea.)
My Khe Beach?
This is My Khe Beach.
This is where...
- there are many Koreans?
- Yes.
So this is how I'm getting to see a beach.
Is this your first time seeing a beach?
- Yes.
- This year?
It's like Anmok Beach.
It's really nice.
(One of Da Nang's most beloved attractions)
(I like My Khe Beach.)
My Khe Beach is quite nice.
There's a reason why many people visit this place.
Do you see the Buddha statue there?
- At the far end.
- A Buddha statue?
The white one over there. That's famous too.
Seeing My Khe Beach and the Buddha statue together...
is a popular route.
(A must-do for travellers in Da Nang)
There sure are lots of Korean tourists here.
- I see a lot of Korean signs.
- Right?
Yes.
- Da Nang Seafood Paradise.
- Right.
It's written in Korean.
They're all written in Korean.
There are a lot of Koreans.
We won't be going there.
Right.
(The travel buddies must stick to their standard.)
(Mỳ Quảng, My Khe Beach, Sơn Trà)
There are a lot of people.
Are they all locals?
If you look around,
there are many cars.
You may think it's a crowded place,
but they're all Vietnamese people.
You don't find a single Korean.
There's no Korean.
- There's a monkey.
- What?
There's a monkey.
What?
- It looks like a baby.
- A baby?
- Where did it go?
- Right here. Goodness.
What are they doing?
Goodness.
- This one looks like the leader.
- Yes.
- There's a baby.
- A baby?
- It's a baby.
- The one at the back.
I guess they're a family.
(Monkeys welcome you Bán Đảo Sơn Trà.)
I've never seen them from this close.
What is this? Is this a zoo?
The baby.
(Moving)
Goodness. What is he doing?
(Getting startled)
He's worried we might hurt his baby.
That's cool.
He's trying to guard his baby.
I really love the eyes.
They're saying, "I'll protect my family."
(I'll protect my family!)
I wonder if we'll see many of them at the beach.
We have to look for the yellow tree.
The one painted in yellow?
Yes.
(Where would the yellow tree be?)
It's like we've entered a jungle.
There aren't any Koreans here.
Right.
This is interesting.
(There isn't a single Korean among all these people.)
- It's over there!
- What's there?
- The tree.
- It's over there!
This is it.
You need to look for this tree.
How is it at the center?
Look for a beach with no Koreans.
Bãi Da.
(Bãi Da)
(As they walk along the long, winding path)
Look at the entrance.
Who would know about this among tourists here?
It's amazing.
It's nice because it looks like untouched nature.
Right.
It looks natural.
(Screaming)
(They can hear excited squeals from a distance.)
It's the sound of the locals.
I can see the beach!
There are quite a few people here.
The locals.
What?
Yes. Nice view.
No wonder there aren't many people.
- How would people know this place?
- They wouldn't.
How would they come here?
They really wouldn't know.
(Bai Da Beach, Da Nang's hidden gem)
Bai Da.
They really wouldn't know.
(Bai Da Beach, Da Nang's hidden gem)
Bai Da.
It's like a private beach.
(Instead of the landmark everyone visits...)
(They came to a real local spot only locals know of.)
(This is fun!)
It's just like how we went to the beach when we were young.
(Bai Da Beach, Da Nang's hidden gem)
(Da Nang locals relaxing by the calm sea)
Look over there.
- Right. It's a wedding photo shoot.
- Wedding...
A wedding photo shoot.
(It's a famous spot for wedding photo shoots.)
(This is Hyunmoo Road)
We're not going to My Khe Beach.
- We're going to Bai Da Beach.
- Bai Da Beach.
(Bai Da Beach)
They're all Vietnamese.
It's a Vietnamese vacation spot.
It's a vacation spot for families.
(If you're tired of the busy sightseeing,)
(head to Bai Da Beach for a quiet rest.)
That looks like fun.
- They're riding pedal boats.
- Yes.
There's a banana boat that's going over there.
They all look like fun.
- Do you like them all?
- Yes.
I think...
if we talk to the place that looks like the headquarters,
we can decide what activities we want to do.
We can decide the spot we'll use too.
(The vacationers have settled between the rocks.)
This looks like the best spot.
- This spot is nice.
- Right here.
It looks expensive.
It might not be that expensive.
(Hyun Moo wants this spot.)
- Xin chào.
- Hello. Xin chào.
(Do you want to take that spot?)
- How much is it?
Hai Trăm dong.
- Two hundred thousand.
How much is 200,000 dong?
It's about 10 dollars.
That's quite nice.
(Until sunset)
All day?
(For 10 dollars, they can enjoy the prime beach spot all day.)
What about this?
- All inclusive.
Free?
(Getting flustered)
Ba trăm một người.
It's 300,000 dong per person.
Then that's 15 dollars.
It's 15 dollars.
- Okay.
- All day.
Let's go, all-day project!
(Total: 800,000 dong, which is approximately 40 dollars)
(Let's go to our prime spot!)
Yes!
How is this best spot empty?
(Hyun Moo can't believe this luck.)
- This is nice.
- Yes.
(Lying down)
This is so nice.
This is what I've been dreaming about.
(The perfect rest Hyun Moo dreamed of)
How do Koreans not know this place?
We have to go barefoot...
from here.
Of course.
We should go barefoot. This is a luxury.
I'll remove them.
Should I go down there and have some fun?
Have fun.
You can do the activities when you want to.
Really?
It looked like you had to wear life jackets.
(He wore it.)
It's raining.
(It was hot all day long.)
(Vietnam's heat just wouldn't let up.)
(A welcome rain to cool things down)
The rain feels so nice.
(Even a rainy beach is a playground for them.)
(Joon is just happy about the cool rain.)
(Feeling refreshed)
I don't have extra clothes.
I'm going shirtless for the first time in a while.
What am I going to do about the maesaengi?
(Sealing the maesaengi)
(The path to the beach seems a bit rough.)
If you take off your shoes from there...
(Trying not to laugh)
It would hurt.
I should have worn my slippers.
Shall we go inside?
- Is it cold?
- The water is cool!
- Isn't it cold?
- It's perfect.
- You're lying.
- It's not cold.
Really.
You have to enter at once.
It's so nice!
- It's too...
- I'm serious.
It's really okay.
Trust me. It's really nice.
(Dipping himself)
My butt feels cold.
- It's so nice.
- Stop lying.
It's so nice.
My stomach stings.
(He gets inside in the end.)
(The water is jade-blue.)
- It's refreshing.
You look so cool.
You look like you're the only one floating in the sea.
(Let's head out into the open sea!)
(Having an underwater date)
(What a sight.)
They're really having fun.
How nice. This is nice.
This is nice.
There really aren't any Koreans here.
I feel so much at ease.
What's with that Gangnam Style?
(Is that a Korean person?)
(Does this place not meet the Hyunmoo Road standard?)
- She's not Korean, right?
- She's not.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Korea!
- Korea.
Are you a family?
Yes. We're a family.
We're from Phu Quoc Island.
- Phu...
- Phu Quoc Island.
- Bugok Hawaii?
- Ho Chi Minh.
Ho Chi Minh!
- Phu Quoc Island.
I love Ho Chi Minh.
How long have you been here?
- This is my second day.
- Second day.
I speak a little Korean.
- A little.
Very good.
This place is mostly visited by the locals.
You don't find tourists.
The Bai Da Beach isn't very well known yet.
(Only Da Nang locals enjoyed such a nice place.)
It's my first time seeing Koreans here.
(Welcome!)
(They became the first Korean visitors to Bai Da Beach.)
What do you want to do first?
The paddle boat first.
(Screaming)
I...
- This...
- Okay.
We're not supposed to face each other.
This is a must-do for couples.
Right.
(In between the couples...)
Everyone here is a couple except us.
(The only ones showing off their bromance)
This isn't something for two men.
Goodness.
Why did I come here with a man?
You look cool right now.
Make sure my belly doesn't show.
I'll focus on your upper body. Your face...
(It's still quite fun for two men to enjoy.)
Can we go farther? Should we go?
I can paddle with power.
(Paddling with power in the same spot)
Are we going forward or not?
Do you want to switch?
You might get a role in a drifting movie.
(He starts with strong paddling.)
That's good paddling. Keep going forward!
(We set sail!)
(Captain Moo Sparrow)
(The muscular sailor, Lee Joon)
(The Paddleboard Pirates set sail.)
(Hyun Moo and Joon cleave through the water.)
(The two pirates' song echoes through Bai Dai Beach.)
(Let's keep going.)
(They've come pretty far, thanks to Joon.)
To the vast sea!
You look...
like a guy who's actually cast away.
("Cast Away by Jun")
Wilson!
(They've completely adjusted to Bai Dai Beach.)
Let's go!
(Speeding up)
- It's scary!
- No!
It's so scary.
This is way too scary!
- It's so scary!
- No!
Let's go that way.
(Speeding)
I'm so scared!
- No!
- That's scary.
It's faster than I thought.
(A thrilling ride through the waves)
(Happy)
Don't do it!
I'm scared.
I've been trained for this in Gangwon Province.
(Singing the theme song of "Pirates of the Caribbean" again)
(Diving passionately)
I'm alive.
I still live!
(They're having as much fun as we're having.)
Joon, there's a shower.
Let's wash up.
Yes, it's too salty.
It's so cold!
Oh, man.
It's too cold.
(Making a fuss)
(The body of a man who works out and a man who doesn't)
I look so small next to him.
(It's not that fancy, but at least we can shower.)
(The water must be a bit cold.)
Don't you crave something sweet because it's too salty?
I do.
I'd like some fruit.
That stings.
I should wear my pyjamas.
(Pyjamas?)
I wear this to bed.
- Is it the same one again?
- It's for bed.
I can wash it at home.
What's the difference between pyjamas and outside clothes?
They're the same once I wash them.
All done.
- I'm all refreshed now.
- That's refreshing.
How long were we out there? It felt long.
A day goes by fast.
It's been so long since I last had fun in the water.
Same here.
I haven't had that much fun in so long.
(They hear music from somewhere.)
It's pretty similar.
When we go to a place like this in Korea, there's trot music.
I know, right?
- It's...
- That was fun.
how we went on vacation in the 1980s.
We went to the beach, laid mats,
and ate watermelons.
We'd have braised chicken back in the day.
- Because we could cook as well.
- Exactly.
We had portable burners, right?
(And the way they sit together and share delicious food)
It's the same.
How are people so similar?
(The daily lives that go across borders)
It feels nice.
Playing in the water does make you hungry.
(Did you say you were hungry?)
- Hello.
(They see a fruit seller who's passing by.)
What would you like?
(In Vietnam, street vendors known as "Hang Rong" allow you...)
(to buy fruit, snacks, and daily necessities...)
(right on the street.)
- Sweet?
- Pardon?
- Is it sweet?
- Sweet?
It's sweet? Okay.
- And...
- Mango.
- Mango?
- Yes.
That's a mango.
- Okay.
- How much is it?
- It's 20,000 dong for 1.
Thank you.
Let's see.
(Crunch)
This doesn't taste like mango.
What is it, then?
This is a mango?
It tastes like an apple.
(Frowning)
- It's sour, isn't it?
- It's not ripe yet.
It gets soft when it's ripe, right?
I've never had a mango like this.
(Green mango is crunchy and sour.)
I went to Mexico, and I realised...
people who lived in hot countries...
dipped sweet fruit in salt.
- They dip mango in salt?
- Yes.
When you live in a hot country, you sweat a lot,
so you need to replenish sodium.
So, they dip it in salt.
Apparently, Vietnamese students bring this salt when they go abroad.
It's salty and sour.
(He also tries it.)
(Hyun Moo can't handle pungent taste.)
It's too salty.
(Crunching)
You seem to eat it well.
It's not that bad.
It's not as sweet as I expected.
Right.
This is sweeter.
Is this a coconut? What is it?
Try it. It's way sweeter.
What's this?
It's a jackfruit.
- Oh, this is a jackfruit?
- What?
(He's never heard of it.)
- Jackfruit.
- I've never heard of it before.
(What lies under the rugged skin will surprise you.)
It's good.
(Jackfruit is special for its chewiness and sweetness.)
It's far sweeter and better.
The fruit vendors must make a lot of money.
You can't help but crave it after playing in the water.
We don't get this in Korea,
- so it's more interesting...
- Right.
when I eat it here.
(Lying down)
- Oh, boy.
- I love it.
(He's at an age where he just wants to lie down after eating.)
(Joon also lies down.)
This is what I call vacation.
(The finishing touch to a vacation is a nap.)
(They relax, listening to the waves...)
(that sound like a lullaby.)
(The locals have a culture of taking naps to avoid the heat.)
(They join the locals, facing the sea breeze.)
(Opening his eyes)
Why am I so sleepy?
- Right?
- I dozed off twice.
(I thought I was dreaming mid-day.)
I didn't play that hard, even when I was little.
(He never played pirate, even when he was a child.)
I don't think I've ever done that.
But that freedom...
was something that we desired...
from a primitive level.
- We played so childishly.
- We did.
It brought back memories from high school.
I felt like a high school student.
We fell in the water, giggled about it,
and threw each other into the ocean.
I felt liberated.
(It was all the more liberating due to the rain.)
Although it was childish, it was so much fun.
It was like I took a nice break with a good friend.
(Their trip begins now.)
(Travel itinerary available on our official social media account)
(Don't come any closer.)
(I'm so tired.)
(Panting)
(A mysterious run in the middle of the night)
(Screaming)
(Feeling liberated in a foreign country)
(I'll be 50 in 2 years.)
(It tastes better without underwear.)
That's hot!
(It's true that you come to Vietnam to eat.)
(I booked a train.)
The next station is...
(Huế)
(Gyeongju of Vietnam)
(Where the time of the last dynasty lingers)
(What looks like a normal train...)
(holds a surprise inside?)
- Look at that. That's gorgeous.
- Stunning.
(What's wrong?)
(What's going on?)
(People start heading somewhere.)
(The two follow them as if they're possessed.)
(They start dancing at 7am?)
(Is it a surprise dance-off?)
(No, they're uniting through dance.)
(Whatever you expect, it will be better.)
(An unpredictable road trip)
We're the only ones on a rickshaw.
It's really good.
Really good!